

CONTACT

Mobile: +49 177 4778 501 E-mail: giorgio.torre8@gmail.com Location: Munich, Germany

EXPERIENCE

stellenanzeigen.de

Junior Software Developer December 2020 - current

Bombardier Transportation UK

Project Commercial Manager September 2016 - May 2021

EDUCATION

Cranfield University (UK)

MSc in Manufacturing Systems September 2014 - August 2015

Pisa University (IT)

BSc & MSc in Industrial Engineering September 2010 - August 2014

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English / Italian
Native / Bilingual proficiency

German

Professional working proficiency

GIORGIO TORRE

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a self-taught software developer. I love challenges, problem-solving and projects delivery. I am a self-starter who loves to learn new skills and improve existing ones. My professional and life experiences brought to me a solid blend of technical knowledge and project delivery awareness, a great combination in today's fast-paced work environment.

SKILLS

- TypeScript / JavaScript
- React / Next.js / Remix.run
- HTML5 / CSS3 / Styled Components / SASS
- Redux / Redux Toolkit
- Jest / React Testing Library

PROJECTS

Personal Portfolio

Stack: React / React Router / SASS

Fully responsive personal portfolio app showcasing my work https://towerbrother.github.io/portfolio-app

Weather App

Stack: React / SASS

Simple weather forecast application for retrieving data from OpenWeatherAPI - https://towerbrother.github.io/weather-app

JavaScript Calculator

Stack: HTML / CSS / Javascript

Simple, modern-looking calculator coded with Vanilla JS - https://towerbrother.github.io/JS-calculator

LINKS

https://github.com/towerbrother/ https://towerbrother.github.io/portfolio-app/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/giorgiotorre/